2minutesurvey.co.uk 2010-06-04

# Fair Exchange Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy - Last updated November 2008.  

PDV Ltd operates the Fair Exchange Programme and is the Data Controller.

PDV Ltd takes the protection of your privacy very seriously and this Privacy Policy sets out how PDV Ltd will use the information you have provided through your interaction with any of the Fair Exchange data collection properties.

PDV is registered in the United Kingdom under the Data Protection Act 1998 (registration Z720633X) and we adhere to the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.

PDV Ltd is a full member of the Direct Marketing Association (DMA).

PDV’s registered office Green Heys, Walford Road, Ross on Wye, HR9 5DB, is registered in England under the Companies Act 2006 under registration number 3974954. VAT registration number is 761423151

We promise our users that we will: 

  * Protect any personal data that we gather
  * Adhere to the principles of permission marketing*
  * Be clear about how we use the information we collect
  * Deal promptly and honestly with any complaints about our practices
  * Be a champion of consumer data protection
  * Endeavour to provide you with a personalised experience

And that we will not 

  * Send you offers without your permission
  * Release personal information about you unless it is 
    * With your permission
    * To a third party who works with us under strict contractual terms to deliver our service to you

***Permission marketing means that when you join the Fair Exchange Programme you agree that we and our partner companies may use the details you supply to decide which offers may interest you most and then to get in touch with you about these offers, via post, e-mail, text or telephone. You can specify that you do NOT wish to be contacted by a specific method by logging on to MY PROFILE and clicking whichever options best suit you. PDV Ltd may, also use information about you from other suppliers to provide all of part of its service to you.**

Our websites will form the Fair Exchange Programme are:

Chooseaprize.com, Thedailydraw.com, Scratchandmatch.com, Fruitillion.com,Strikermillion.com, Prizetag.com, Winaflat.com, Winferraris.com, Fair-exchange.com, free-dvd-club.com

Information about you will be collected initially when you join the Fair Exchange Programme and will involve contact information (e.g. age and gender). This information will be used to identify offers that may be of interest to you.

Through your interaction with the Fair Exchange Programme, there may be occasions where additional personal information is collected through surveys, questionnaires, offers or competitions. This information provided by you may be shared with our commercial partners.

Our websites provide links to our partner sites. These links will lead you to websites operated by third parties that operate under different Privacy Policies. Should you choose one of these links you will be leaving a PDV Ltd site for a site over which we have no control and we therefore accept no liability once you have left one of our sites.

**WHEN YOU LEAVE OUR WEBSITE, THE PRIVACY POLICY ON THE SITE YOU HAVE MOVED TO MAY NOT BE THE SAME AS OURS, SO IF YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE USED BY THE BUSINESS CONTROLLING THAT SITE, BE SURE TO READ ITS PRIVACY POLICY**

PDV Ltd works with many partners to deliver offers to you that we believe may be of interest given the information you have provided.

By joining the Fair Exchange Programme through any of our data collection methods, you are agreeing that you are happy for us and our partner companies to use your details to decide which offers may interest you most and then to get in touch with you about these offers, via post, e-mail, text or telephone.

PDV Ltd may, from time to time, use third party suppliers to provide all of part of its service to you. PDV Ltd shall only be entitled to disclose such of your personal information as is necessary to enable them to provide the relevant service to you.

PDV Ltd strongly supports the principles of ‘permission marketing’ and will only send communications from itself and its partners with your agreement.

When you first register with us you agree to receive e-mails, postal communications, text and phone communications. You can specify that you do NOT wish to be contacted by a specific method by logging on to MY PROFILE and clicking whichever options best suit you.

We hope you will enjoy the communications we send you, but if at any time you change your mind, you may withdraw these permissions AT ANY TIME by either:

  * Going to the MY PROFILE page within any of our sites and ticking the relevant ‘NO’ box.
  * Using the ‘unsubscribe’ link on any of the e-mail messages we send you.

If you prefer you may change your mind or stop all further communication (there may be a short delay) by writing to: The Data Protection Compliance Officer, PDV Ltd, 3rd Floor, 64 Clarendon Road, Watford, Hertfordshire, WD17 1DA. This is also the contact point if you have any complaint about our service.

If we do not hear otherwise from you, we will assume that the information you provide to us is accurate and up-to-date and we will continue to use the information to send you the communications you have requested.

Please note that PDV Ltd will act in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and remove your permission as promptly as possible but you could continue to receive communications for a short period of time whilst this change is actioned.

You have a right under the Data Protection Act 1998 to see what information we hold about you, subject to certain conditions. 

Our websites provide you with direct access to your contact details which you may update at any time but should you make an application to us in writing, we may ask you to provide us with sufficient information so that we can be sure that you are who you say you are as we cannot act on requests for access to personal data from third parties. We also reserve the right to make a small charge for providing you with the information you are requesting.

If you would like to proceed with a request to see what data we hold about you, please write to the Data Protection Compliance Officer, PDV Ltd, 3rd Floor, 64 Clarendon Road, Watford, Hertfordshire, WD17 1DA.

When you give your personal data to PDV Ltd we will process that data in accordance with our responsibilities under the Data Protection Act 1998, and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) 2003 and other legislation if it is relevant.

We will keep your data safe and secure. To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct usage of information, we monitor and adjust our physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safegard and secure your personal data while in our care, or in the care of any outside suppliers with whom we may contract to process your data on our behalf. 

Whilst we strive to protect your personal information, the internet is not a 100% secure medium for communication and, accordingly, PDV Ltd cannot guarantee the security of any information you send PDV via the internet. PDV Ltd is not responsible for any loss or damage that you or others may suffer as a result of loss of confidentiality of such information.

You must type in a correct password to access your Fair Exchange account and details. It is your responsibility to ensure the security of your Fair Exchange password and not to reveal this information to others.

Cookies are small files of letters and numbers downloaded onto your computer when you access certain websites. Cookies unlock a computer’s memory allowing sites to recognise users when they return to a site. Like a key, a cookie itself does not contain information but when it is read by a browser it can help a website identify you and your requirements.

PDV Ltd uses cookies as a means of limiting the number of times you may see a certain advertisement on your screen (a process called frequency capping) to ensure that you see the best range of relevant offers and adverts.

PDV Ltd also uses ‘web beacons’ as a means of tracking whether or not you open e-mails from us. This information is used to assess whether the message has been effective, both for you and us or our partners. The information is retained by us and used in deciding the most appropriate offers to be made to you in the future.

In some cases, we also track the pages visited when you click through from Fair Exchange to one of our partner sites. Note that this information is

  * Anonymous – no personal information is released or can be derived from it
  * Restricted only to our sites and the sites of our partners. We do not track pages you visit on the general internet.

Some of the partners that we advertise with require us to use cookies or action tags. These action tags provide those websites with the aggregate number of registrations to enable them to evaluate the effectiveness of their advertising. In some instances, we and another business may exchange some of your information as part of this assessment and the provision of rewards to you. The specific details should be explained in the ‘Privacy Policy’ or ‘Conditions of Use’ page of the partner sites.

Some of the partner websites that advertise with us via our games, competitions and e-mails may well use cookies within their sites.

You may decide how you wish cookies to be used. You can make and action this decision within your computer and you can easily delete cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser.

Most industry-standard web browsers have an option that allows you to turn off all cookies or have your computer inform you each time that a request to place a cookie is being made. If you turn cookies off (or refuse to accept a request to place a cookie) you may not have access to some features on our websites and our partners’ websites and you may lose the functionality of locating some of our services.

If you would like more information about cookies and how to control them no matter what version and which software you are using, go to  
www.allaboutcookies.org 

PDV Ltd is not liable for information that is inaccurate due to technical defects in software used on our websites, whether induced by our systems or by software provided by third parties.

By using our websites you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. PDV Ltd reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time. Visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time-to-time to stay abreast of any changes. Your continued use of our websites following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept those changes. 

PDV Ltd will undertake to revise the ‘last updated’ statement at the top and bottom of the Privacy Policy in the event of any changes to the Policy in the future.

Last Updated November 2008.
